## Jessica Cosio

604 Bush St. #203 San Francisco, CA 94108

M (805) 865-6148 E jessica.cosio@icloud.com

Profile

My time in San Francisco came about a bit over 4 years ago with a job offer at Macy's Inc. I was immediately given the opportunity to develop front facing technology for this exciting company that leads in consumer retail. I made it! That's honestly how I've been feeling since I started my job. Working in a big company has led to being assigned to a variety of projects and working alongside great teams. I still enjoy my work, but I also understand that new journeys await, and that other opportunities will make for more stimulating experiences. That is why you are reading this document and the reason for my interest in working with you.



Experience

Software Engineer, Macy's Inc. San Francisco, CA - Aug 2015-Present

- Full stack web development for the single page mobile web app, m.macys.com
- \* A/B Testing and KPI tracking through web analytics implementations
- \* Analytics using IBM coremetrics
- High Priority urgent code delivery and defect fixes
- \* Feature/kill switch design and implementation
- Unit test coverage and performance test baselining behind delivered features
- \* Strong emphasis on process and delivery- especially using lean principles
- \* Strategical retail technology research- emphasis on UX implications
- Daily documentation of work as a personal practice
- Weekly retrospective and showcase of work to business stakeholders

Tech Star Executive Development Program, Macy's Inc. San Francisco, CA - Aug 2015-Jan 2016

- Balance platform development with human resources managed training sessions
- Deliver monthly showcase to program stakeholders, managers, and colleagues
- \* Assignment to mobile platform and content engineering teams create common components for web development, execute library updates

Software Intern, Autoliv -Night Vision Goleta, CA - Jun 2015-Aug 2015

- \* Ensure validity of gain calibration testing software used to validate night vision cameras on the production line
- \* Create test documentation for verification of calibration software
- Develop small scripts as necessary

Education

California Polytechnic State University, San Luis Obispo, CA – B.S. Software Engineering, Winter 2015

Skills

full-stack, front-end/UI, web development, javascript, node, HTML, CSS/SCSS, SASS, responsive design, git, npm, typescript, firebase, java, SQL, python, PHP, unix, IoT, express, google cloud, aws, angular, backbone, jboss, maven

**Projects** 

Macy's Store Hub (present), Omniclient Stylist Tool (present), Macy's Voice Lab (2018), Shoppable Content Lean Lab (2018), Mobile Web Innovation Lean Lab (2016-2018), Google AMP Hackathon-NYC (2018), Macy's Hackathon-Top 5 (2017), Macy's Idea Lab - Online Tuxedo Rental Tool (2016), Mobile Web Platform (2015), EDP Class of Fall 2015

References

Ray Hunter (970) 460-6046 colleague Keith Abdulla (650) 276-8167 tech lead

Lemel Williams (213) 784-8802 tech lead Dora Do (510) 449-9802 colleague